Guide to the Van Cleef Family papers, 1841-1935
Van Cleef Family papers, 1841-1935
- Series I. Mynderse Van Cleef's Business and Professional Correspondence
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (A-B), 1913-1914 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (A-B), 1914 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (K-M), 1913-1914 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (N-P), 1913-1914 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (Q-S), 1913-1914 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (S), 1913-1914 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - M. Van Cleef's business and professional correspondence with the Ithaca Trust Company (S-Z), 1913-1918 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (A-B), 1908-1918 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (C-J), 1909-1918 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (K-L), 1914 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (M-Q), 1908-1918 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (R-S), 1914-1919 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (S), 1908-1913 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees (T-Z), 1909-1915 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1908-1910 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1908-1910 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence with the Cornell University Board of Trustees, 1908-1910 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between M. Van Cleef and J.G. Schurman (former president of Cornell University), 1908-1910 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between J.G. Schurman, M. Van Cleef and Theodore Stanton, 1908-1909 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Griswold Worsted Company Limited-business correspondence, 1901-1903 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Griswold Worsted Company Limited-business correspondence, 1902 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Griswold Worsted Company Limited-business correspondence, 1902-1903 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Griswold Worsted Company Limited-business correspondence, 1902-1903 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Griswold Worsted Company Limited-business correspondence, 1902-1903 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (A-B)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 1901-1902 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (C-M)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 1901-1902 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (N-X)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 1901-1902 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (A-F)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 1902-1903 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (G-J)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 19002-1903 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (K-Q)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 1902-1903 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - M. Van Cleef's business correspondence (R-S)-J.C. Stowell Estate, 1902-1903 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - B.G. Wilder correspondence, 1896 & 1908 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - M. Van Cleef's personal receipted bills, 1935-1938 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - The Estate of Sarah E. Wilgus-miscellaneous papers, 1877 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - The Estate of Sarah E. Wilgus-miscellaneous papers, 1911-1922 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - The Estate of Sarah E. Wilgus-miscellaneous papers, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Estate of Sarah E. Wilgus-miscellaneous papers, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1900-1904 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1901 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1905-1910 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1910-1915 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1911-1914 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation- correspondence with Charles H. Blood, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1914-1915 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1915-1916 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1916-1918 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1918-1919 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the Cayuga Lake Cement Corporation, 1918-1919 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - A bound black copy book of M. Van Cleef's letters, 1891-1909 (Box 21)
- Series II. Ithaca Water Works Co.
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous pamphlets, 1905-1906 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca Water Works Corporation-blueprints, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca Water Works Corporation, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ithaca Water Works Corporation, 1902-1905 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous documents, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ithaca Water Works Corporation-pictures (copies) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1903-1905 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1903-1904 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1905-1906 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 19054-1906 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1904-1906 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1907-1910 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca-miscellaneous legal documents and letters, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Ithaca Water Works Co. versus the City of Ithaca, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Series III. The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1902-1907 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1904-1905 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1904-1907 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1907-1908 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1909-1912 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1907-1913 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - The People of the State of New York vs. Brooklyn Cooperage Co. and Cornell University, 1907-1913 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Series IV. The Estate of Joseph Esty
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- securities, 1896-1904 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- securities, 1881-1919 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- his original will and securities, 1878-1918 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- legal indentures, 1838-1866 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- legal indentures, 1838-1881 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- legal indentures and balance sheets, 1862-1916 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- balance sheets, 1883-1895 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- legal indentures, 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers- legal indentures, 1820-1864 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers-legal indentures, 1851-1871 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers-legal indentures, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty papers-bills, 1903-1908 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-bills, 1908-1909 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-bills, 1909-1910 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-bills, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1892-1899 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1899-1901 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1901-1903 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty-, 1903-1905 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1909-1911 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1912-1915 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous documents and letters from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1917-1919 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-miscellaneous documents and letters, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-ledger book (Box 8)
  - List of securities and property belonging to the Estate of Joseph Esty (bound book) (Box 8)
  - Joseph Esty's rent book and memorandum, 1868-1905 (Box 8)
  - Six check books from the estate of Joseph Esty, 1891-1910 (Box 8)
  - Joseph Esty's day book, 1881-1909 (Box 8)
  - Surrogate Court in the matter of the final judicial settelement of the acounts of Joseph Esty (Box 8)
  - Four photographs of E.S. Esty (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous prints (Box 8)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-letter book, 1889-1900 (Box 9)
  - The Estate of Joseph Esty-miscellaneous papers in regards to accounting of trustees, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Estate of Joseph Esty-miscellaneous papers in regards to accounting of trustees, 1889-1900 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Estate of Joseph Esty-ledger (Box 28)
- Series V. Ithaca Security Company
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1905-1908 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1914-1916 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ithaca Security Company correspondence and documents, 1913-1919 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Stock book from the Ithaca Security Company, 1905 (Box 11)
  - Ithaca Security Company's day book, 1905-1919 (Box 11)
  - Ithaca Security Company's ledger book, 1907-1910 (Box 11)
- Series VI. Mynderse Van Cleef's Court Decisions and Legal Documents
  - Book containing the accounts of the estates of Samuel H. Wilcox, Timothy D. Wilcox and Margaret A. Wilcox, 1885-1887 (Box 11)
  - A book containing a list of securities belonging to Margaret A. Wilcox (Box 11)
  - Cash book of M. Van Cleef, trustee of the estate of Harrick Wheatley (Box 11)
  - M. Van Cleef's printed court decisions, 1867-1908 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - M. Van Cleef's printed court decisions, 1867-1906 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - M. Van Cleef's printed court decisions, 1876 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - M. Van Cleef's printed court decisions, 1867-1897 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - M. Van Cleef's printed court decisions, 1892-1895 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - M.Van Cleef's miscellaneous legal and court documents, 1874-1917 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Drawings of Cornell University's Kappa Alpha Fraternity, 1876 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts, 1921-1927 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1873-1907 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous printed court decisions (Box 12)
  - Materials pertaining to the estate of Leonard Treman; three bound books, 1888-1895 (Box 12)
  - Account books from the estate of Leonard Treman, 1889-1897 (Box 12)
  - Three small bound books from the estate of Leauder R. King (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1855-1865 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1856-1881 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1862-1885 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1868-1881 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1880-1883 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1880-1889 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1903-1904 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1888-1892 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents and business correspondence, 1891-1897 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous business documents and correspondence, 1903-1904 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents and business correspondence, 1896-1904 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents pertaining to the establishement of a College of Forestry at Cornell University, 1898 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents pertaining to the establishment of the College of Forestry at Cornell University, 1898 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Briefing documents pertaining to the court case of the City of Ithaca v. the Ithaca City Water Works Co. (Box 13)
  - A briefing document pertaining to the court case of the Gardner Water Company v. the Inhabitants of the Town of Gardner (Box 13)
  - A briefing document pertaining to the court case of Cornell University v. the Denny Hotel Company of Seattle (Box 13)
  - A pamphlet entitled "Liberty" by Henry Bool (Box 13)
  - The Fish and Game Law, 1894 (Box 13)
  - An indenture of the Ithaca Traction Corporation (Box 13)
  - The Estate of John C. and C.D. Stowell, 1896-1904 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - The Estate of Samuel D.Wilcox, 1883-1893 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Estate of Samuel D.Wilcox, 1877-1884 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The Estate of Samuel D.Wilcox, 1875-1884 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Estate of Harriet Wheatley, 1868-1884 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The Estate of Harriet Wheatley, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Estate of Harriet Wheatley, 1886 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Estate of Leonard and Almira Treman, 1883-1888 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The Estate of Leonard and Almira Treman-vouchers, 1885-1900 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - The Estate of Eliza C. Hazen, 1883-1891 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - The Estate of Eliza C. Hazen, Wilgus Minors, 1882 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Estate of Eliza C. Hazen, Wilgus Minors, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Wilgus Family Papers, 1883-1885 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Celadon Roofing Tile Co. brochure, 1899 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Raymond and Whitcomb Co. brochure & Costikyan Bros. and Co. brochure, 1908 and Spring 1902 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Art in Wood" brochure, "Wood Mantles" brochure and "Parquetry" brochure (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "Burrowe's Wire Screens for Windows and Doors" brochure [The E.T. Burrowes Co.], 1899-1902 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Gasoline Motors and Launches" brochure [Fay and Bowen] (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Royal Carbon Paint" brochure (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Burrowe's Perfected Screens" brochure (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Yachts and Launches" brochure [The Michigan Yacht and Power Co.] (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - F.P. Smith's Wire and Iron Works Catalogue, 1904 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Sagendorph's Patent Metal Sectional Ceilings and Side Walls" brochures (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Ithaca Electric Light and Power Company" brochure (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Illustrated Catalogue No. 157 of Fine Fishing Tackle (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - "Portland Cement as an Investment" brochure (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous business cards (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence to M. Van Cleef, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Two programs of performances by the Cornell Masque- "Oolong" and Panatela", 1907 and 1909 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous abstracts of titles from court cases (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous abstracts of titles from court cases (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous abstracts of titles from court cases (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous court records and documents, 1891-1924 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - M. Van Cleef's miscellaneous statements, 1924-1929 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - M. Van Cleef's miscellaneous statements, 1929-1933 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - M. Van Cleef's nomination for the office of Trustee of Cornell University-note to the alumni, 1886 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - M. Van Cleef's nomination for the office of Trustee of Cornell University-note to the alumni, 1886 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - M. Van Cleef's miscellaneous notes and documents pertaining to his nomination as Trustee of Cornell University (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors of the County of Tompkins, 1893 (Box 23)
  - Carrie M. Kellogg against industrial benefit association appeals book (Box 23)
  - Charles R. True vs. the Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. points for appellant (Box 23)
  - Who's Who in New York [M. Van Cleef, R.H. Treman, C.E. Treman and J.G. Schurman are included], 1914 (Box 23)
  - A red bound book of court teminology (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous court indenture and documentation (Box 23)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-The Esty Estate, 1883-1900 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-Supreme Court documents, 1882-1883 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-Supreme Court documents, 1847-1882 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Van Cleef papers concerning the Lyceum Opera Theatre, 1893-1909 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-Supreme Court documents, 1884-1896 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-The Esty Estate, 1896-1897 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-Supreme Court indentures, 1900-1903 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-Supreme Court documents, 1906-1920 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef's papers-Supreme Court documents, 1883-1900 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Series VII. The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy
  - Miscellaneous bills and correspondence from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1878-1888 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1878-1888 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous legal papers from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1879-1880 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1882-1886 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1882-1890 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy-, 1883-1884 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1883-1885 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1884-1887 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1884-1889 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous bills and correspondence from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1884-1891 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous bills and correspondence from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1884-1891 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1886-1890 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1886-1890 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1887 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous bills and correspondence from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1878-1889 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1887-1896 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1888-1889 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1888-1890 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1888-1891 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1887-1896 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1890-1891 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1890-1891 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - The Estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1890-1892 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1891 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1891 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1892-1893 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous bills and receipts from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1893-1894 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous papers from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1894-1895 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous papers from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1895 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous papers from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1894-1895 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous papers from the estate of Frederick Lovejoy, 1895 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - A bound book of the copies of Frederick Lovejoy's letters, 1874-1878 (Box 18)
  - Two bound book copies of Frederick Lovejoy's letters, 1883-1884 (Box 20)
  - A book of Frederick Lovejoy's expenditures (Box 20)
  - A book containing information from the Bank of the State of New York concerning the Estate of Frederick Lovejoy (Box 20)
  - Numerous receipts, checks and bank statements (Box 20)
- Series VIII. Mynderse Van Cleef and Cornell University
  - State Agricultural College-Cornell University, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - State Agricultural College-Cornell University, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - State Agricultural College-Cornell University, 1914-1916 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Building the Kappa Alpha House, 1899 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Building the Kappa Alpha House, 1899-1901 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous actions and proceedings concerning Cornell University, 1900-1916 (Box 18, Folder 3)